= kisskh.lv =
♪From primal chaos to the starry sky♪
♪In the whole world,
we shall hold the balance♪
♪The cauldron tempers divine blades♪
♪The furnace refines the empty void♪
♪The Way is in mystic fate♪
♪Be brave enough
to split the primal chaos wide open♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel
by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
You brothers
will have plenty of time
to mend the bonds later.
Right now, we must
make good use of this victory.
Who
stopped you from finding your Senior?
Once you become King of East Sea,
and with the Celestial Court's help,
finding someone will be effortless.
And who washed away
all your spiritual power,
and put you through such suffering?
This is a tough spot.
No worries.
Switching to Deep Clean mode.
Here you go.
How is that possible?
How
could it be him?
Your Highness.
Your sense of smell
should be back by now.
Why not try
sniffing out
who he really is?
Changshou.
He's breathing.
Your Highness.
I'm Li Changshou.
Changshou.
I am Li Changshou.
Get closer to me.
You're Changgeng.
He...
He just woke up. How's he out again?
Yunxiao?
Yunxiao.
How is it?
Did you see Jin Chan?
Yunxiao?
She's not Yunxiao.
She was my Master a thousand years ago.
The Demon Emperor, Taiyi.
Ao Guang greets Master.
You shameless traitor.
You dare to show your face again?
The terror from 1,000 years ago,
do you still remember?
Moon Elder, go get the painting.
You are right.
I betrayed you all those years ago.
My crimes deserve a thousand deaths.
But today,
I am willing to redeem myself.
I will follow you, Master.
Even if it costs my life.
Your Majesty.
A fake.
These days,
who doesn't keep a guard up?
Scatter.
What a fine sword.
It has been a thousand years.
[Episode 27]
Your Highness.
You've already lost.
Why bother resisting?
Both of you
are going to die.
Your Highness.
At last, before I die,
I see you as you once were.
Don't talk nonsense.
You won't die.
I'll protect you.
Your Highness.
Seeing you return like this,
I can die with no regrets.
Si'er,
that's why you need to stay alive.
We still have
so much time ahead of us.
I have to make it up to you, slowly.
Done with your last words?
Then I'm about to strike.
Live on.
Your Highness.
♪Memories filled with sorrow♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
Your Highness.
You...
Dragon Transformation?
Your Highness.
You are gravely wounded.
If you force the transformation,
aren't you afraid your spiritual power
will collapse and kill you?
No.
You can't control me now.
Are you afraid?
I, Ao Jia,
was bound by your Demonic Arts
and committed countless sins.
Consider this
my way of making amends.
Your Highness,
are you going
to take us both down?
To take the true culprit with me
is worth it.
Your Highness.
Si'er, run!
I won't leave you.
Stay back.
Go find Ao Yi immediately.
He must still be alive.
Tell him,
his brother has failed.
The East Sea Dragon Clan
now rests on his shoulders.
Go!
No.
Now!
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
Your Highness.
Such noble resolve.
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
Ao Jia!
♪Tearfully,
this life's bond is not over♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪
Pity, such a pity.
Such a brave young man.
Yet he couldn't escape destiny.
Truly a fine vessel.
Saves me quite some effort.
Leave Yunxiao's body.
Most people tremble
at the sight of me.
Yet you dare resist?
Get out now.
The Pregenesis Sword is in my hand.
Keeping you is now pointless.
To die at my hand
is your honor.
You dare defy me?
Little brat, run.
Yunxiao.
For him,
you'd resist so stubbornly.
How amusing.
Senior...
It's you.
Why are you in my wedding dress?
You're the Westdawn assassin?
No.
Let go.
Where's Ao Yi?
I'm asking you, where's Ao Yi?
None of your concern.
Who are you?
Why come to the East Sea?
I came for revenge.
You killed Ao Yi?
Didn't you?
Ao Yi can still be saved.
Your Majesty.
Please be careful, Your Majesty.
Turtle.
I am truly useless.
It seems
I'm so old.
No. Your Majesty is ever mighty,
and full of vigor.
Enough.
At a time like this,
stop flattering me.
I know it well.
I've ruled the East Sea
for a thousand years.
I thought I could outplay everyone
and always come out on top.
But the truth is,
I lost this game
long ago.
I was just too arrogant to see it,
so sure I had already won.
Your Majesty.
I made your decoction.
It's almost cold.
Take it while it's warm.
What happened
to you and Yunxiao out there?
How dare you?
Turtle.
What?
The real Pregenesis Sword fragment
was stolen by that Demon Emperor?
I'm asking you.
Wasn't that Demon Emperor
sealed beneath the Eye of the Sea?
He was.
Then why is he possessing Yunxiao?
How much do you know
of the Demon Emperor?
You think that was the Demon Emperor
at full strength?
You're wrong.
That was only a thousandth
of the power he had
a thousand years ago.
A thousand years ago,
this place
was the Demon Emperor's palace.
He united all the demons under his rule,
leaving a trail of blood and death
across the Three Realms.
The Demon Emperor was mighty,
and ruthless beyond measure.
He used the Pregenesis Sword
to counter human magic.
Even the Three Sects joined forces,
yet still could not defeat him.
Back then,
[Demon Emperor Taiyi,]
I was
[Lord of Ancient Demon Court]
his chief general.
But deep down,
I was terrified
of that ruthless tyrant.
Then came the great battle.
Grand Mage Voidcity used his power
to take the Pregenesis Sword
from the Demon Emperor.
With the Human Clan's aid
and my betrayal,
we barely defeated him.
Grand Mage Voidcity
used the Sea-Calming Pillar
to seal the Demon Emperor's body
beneath the Eye of the East Sea.
But at that time, no one noticed
the Demon Emperor left a strand of hair
stuck to Voidcity.
That hair carried
a fragment of his soul.
Years later,
I learned
that the strand had
escaped the East Sea
and hidden in the mountains
in Cattle Land,
where it became a golden lotus.
The Demon Emperor's soul
was hidden inside it
for 1,000 years.
Until one day,
someone picked that lotus.
Who?
I only found out today.
The one who took it
was Jin Chan.
Jin Chan set a deadly trap.
He opened the lotus
and released the Demon Emperor's soul.
It possessed Fairy Yunxiao's body.
But that fragment of his soul
can't wield his full power.
For a thousand years,
the Demon Emperor's body's
thrashed and roared beneath,
raging against his defeat.
He wants to fight again.
He wants back everything he lost.
And he wants to rebuild a Demon Realm
where his kind rules the world.
[Forbidden]
Once the Eye of the Sea is opened,
his soul will burst forth
and fully possess Fairy Yunxiao's body.
By then,
the East Sea will fall.
It will be a Great Tribulation.
Why didn't you stop him at that time?
Stop him?
Only one-thousandth of his power
left us both badly hurt.
Looks like
you truly have no idea
how terrifying the Demon Emperor is.
Yi.
I truly did all I could.
I have guarded the East Sea
for a thousand years,
yet in the end, the East Sea
was still lost at my hands.
I was too proud.
I have brought ruin to the East Sea.
I have doomed Jia.
And you, Yi.
Your Majesty.
You must not blame yourself so.
Turtle.
Just go.
Your Majesty.
Where do you want me to go?
Leave the East Sea.
Find your own safe path.
Your Majesty.
What wrong have I done?
Why drive me out of the East Sea?
I was wrong.
The East Sea's destruction is near.
I am the Dragon King of the East Sea.
I must go down with it.
But you are different.
You smooth-talking Turtle.
You'd thrive anywhere you go.
Why must you stay here
in the East Sea?
Your Majesty.
I've served you a thousand years.
I'd never
find a ruler as wise as you.
You won't leave,
I won't leave either.
You should all leave too.
Destruction of the East Sea
is the Dragon Clan's destiny.
But you are different.
You can flee.
Then flee.
Flee?
Defend the Crystal Palace.
Protect the Dragon King and his son.
Who are you talking to?
Celestial Court soldiers.
What?
How many are there?
One hundred thousand.
One hundred thousand?
From now on, Dragon Palace's security
is fully handled by Celestial Court.
Your Majesty.
You always believed
the Dragon Clan could only survive
by staying neutral.
But you forgot
the value of having allies.
Especially against an enemy
you can't defeat alone.
Sometimes, friends are the only ones
who can give you a chance to survive.
I realized that far too late.
Now Jia is gone,
and Yi…
Once I'm gone,
there'll be no heir left
to the East Sea royal family.
Not necessarily.
How dare you show your face?
Your Highness.
Wake up. Please.
Stop right there.
Uncle...
Arrest her.
Turtle Minister.
Only she can save Ao Yi.
She's the one who assassinated him.
How can we let her near him?
Uncle.
Wake up.
Uncle, where are you?
Senior?
Sorry, Senior.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was you.
That day,
I thought the golden dragon ate you.
I thought the Dragon Clan
killed my family again.
I wanted revenge.
I wanted to avenge you.
It was Changgeng's scheme.
Don't be fooled.
I thought I was getting my revenge.
I never meant to hurt you.
Lies.
All I feel for you is hatred.
Come out, quick.
If you don't, you'll die.
You lied to me.
I will only kill you myself.
Uncle.
Your brother, Ao Jia,
died in battle.
Brother...
Ain't I living just fine?
Brother.
This is Changgeng's scheme.
Don't trust him.
Jin Chan killed him.
Jin Chan is Westdawn's spy
in the East Sea.
Don't trust her.
Don't you trust her.
Uncle.
You said you'd change the Dragon Clan.
Right now, the East Sea Dragon Clan
can only rely on you.
What are you still hiding from?
I believe you'll
change the Dragon Clan for the better
and make sure
the tragedy never happens again.
I trust only you.
You are the only dragon I trust.
I am Ao Yi.
I am Ao Yi, destined to be a light.
He's...
Uncle.
You're finally awake.
Senior.
What's wrong, Senior?
He hasn't quite recovered.
Why did you rush at him?
Move aside, everyone.
Father?
Yi.
My son.
Father.
You finally woke up.
Yi.
My good boy.
You really scared me.
You finally woke up.
Li Changshou.
Your Highness.
About that washing...
Thank you.
You gave me the power I now possess.
You don't blame me for tricking you?
I...
I do blame you.
But without you,
I'd forever be just a little dragon.
Good.
Perfect timing.
I have a surprise for you.
What surprise?
Moon Elder.
Coming.
Moon Elder is here.
Celestial Descent.
Wrong way.
Holding it in so long.
I can finally come out.
I am...
Ke Le'er?
Hua?
Long time no see.
Hua.
Weren't you...
I'm back to life.
How did you come back to life?
Your Highness.
Let me explain to you.
This man right here
is not truly human.
I mean, not a mortal.
Dashing and majestic,
he is the ruler of the Celestial Court.
Haotian, the Celestial Emperor.
Ao Yi greets His Majesty.
Ao Guang greets His Majesty.
Your Majesty, your visit
honors our East Sea.
I... No, no.
On behalf of the East Sea,
I welcome you, Your Majesty.
Dragon King.
Please rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Ke Le'er.
You rise too.
Everyone, please rise.
You can just
call me Hua.
Hua, let me introduce you.
Minister, Si'er.
Senior, come over here.
Allow me to introduce you.
This is Hua,
whom I befriended on Bear Island.
This is Jiang Si'er of the Mermaid Clan.
Buddy,
you arranged all of this, didn't you?
Did you arrange
for Celestial Emperor to appear here
to meet my son?
What?
Not happy about it?
How could I not be happy?
Right now,
the East Sea has Celestial Court's aid.
Even if East Sea falls,
our clan still has somewhere to go.
I can't thank you enough.
Alright, tell me.
What's your escape plan next?
Who said I'm escaping?
You...
I'll face the Demon Emperor head-on.
Did you forget
everything I told you?
I didn't.
You're right.
If I mean to flee,
now is indeed the best time.
The old me
would've bolted long ago.
Then why didn't you?
But it's the Demon Emperor.
He just had to pick someone
he shouldn't have.
Petty trick.
Li Changshou.
Long time no see.
Who are
you again?
You forgot me.
But I've never forgotten you.
My hatred for you
woke me from hell.
Burst.
Villains die from talking too much.
Keep that in mind.
Li Changshou,
I'm the karma of your sins,
the one thing you failed to foresee,
your never-ending nightmare.
In this undead body,
I will forever and ever...
Can you let me finish?
This guy does feel familiar.
Who was he?
I can't recall.
Forget it. Not important.
Ascendance Sect's move?
Good.
Enough talk. Let's fight.
Your opponent is me.
Get out of my way.
Why?
Why can I never beat you?
I refuse to accept it.
That's a wrap for you.
I refuse to accept it!
Yunxiao.
Your Majesty.
What's going on?
The Great Tribulation
has begun.
I've waited for this moment
for ages.
Now, Fairy Yunxiao.
Let it all begin.
A thousand years.
Time to wake up.
Finally, we meet.
Chosen One of Fate.
I am Jin Chan.
♪See mortal joys and sorrows♪
♪Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds♪
♪Alas, love has many twists and turns♪
♪Memories filled with sorrow♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tearfully,
this life's bond is not over♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪
♪Down a few more cups of wine♪
♪Through land and sea,
I ask you to come♪
♪For honor's sake, upright and grand♪
♪Alas, our story is short♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tearfully,
this life's bond is not over♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪